<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Max&#39;s Weblog</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Max&#39;s Weblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SpyxFamily Season 3 is here</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/spyxfamily/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/spyxfamily/</guid>
      <description>The episodes of season 3 of SpyxFamily has started airing. I have been waiting for this season for a almost two years now. And, finally it has arrived. Currently, they have released two episodes and I have watched both of them.&#xA;The first one was not good in my opinion. It was slow paced and felt dull, boring and repetitive. I can&amp;rsquo;t point out which part was repetitive, but it definitely was boring to sit through 20 minutes of that episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabadi vs Muradabadi Biryani</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/biryani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 08:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/biryani/</guid>
      <description>I am living in New Delhi for a month now, and yesterday I got a chance to try the infamous dish, Biryani. In my state, Biryani is not a common dish and cannot be found at the major places, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know how it tastes and what&amp;rsquo;s the standard taste for biryani, but the biryani I ate last night was very flavourful and tasty.&#xA;There were two types of biryani on the shop; Hyderabadi and Muradabadi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom should be the first priority in every aspect of your life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/freedom/</guid>
      <description>I have spent half a decade in academics and I have experienced that there is no freedom in academics and in corporate or any job. You have to follow the retarded rules which lowers your productivity and will to produce something of quality. You have to join mandatory meetings which are not very fruitful and are arranged to just look busy and to fill time. The thing I dislike about the academic life in india is that you have to join useless events which don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to do with your course and they are mandatory to join or you will be sidelined and targetted for not joining them in fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe: Mutton Curry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/mutton-curry-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/mutton-curry-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This is my all time favourite and easy recipe to cook mutton curry. The ingredients can be easily found. This is my first time writing recipe/cooking post, if you want to give me any suggestion or feedback, you can find my email at the bottom of this page. In this recipe, I am using 500g mutton.&#xA;Ingredients:&#xA;500g Mutton 2 Cup Mustard Oil/ Cooking Oil 2 Small to Medium Sized Onion 2 Small to Medium Sized Tomatoes 2 Green Chillies 2 Garlic Cloves 2 Tbsp Yogurt 1 Tbsp Salt 1/2 Turmeric powder 2 Tbsp Kashmiri Red Chilli Powder 2-4 Tbsp Meat Masala 2 Green Cardamom, 2 Cumin and 5-6 Black Pepper First, clean the mutton with water thoroughly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Google account was compromised for 6 months</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/google-account-hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/google-account-hacked/</guid>
      <description>My Google account was compromised for 6 months, and google sent me no security notification regarding this. On 22 Aug, Google sent me a notification that &amp;ldquo;you signed out from your device&amp;rdquo; when I was watching YouTube on my Android device. When I checked in my Google Account dashboard, it showed that my Gmail was logged out from Germany. My Gmail had been logged into that device since Feb, 2025. My Google account has had 2FA enabled for the past four years, since I created this account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Addiction</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/social-media-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/social-media-addiction/</guid>
      <description>Feeling less focused and creative lately. It feels like I am operating on auto-pilot in every aspect of my life. I go to the gym in the morning and there too I feel like I am operating on auto-pilot. I am doing things just for the sake of doing them. I do all these things without getting focused meaning I am not fully focused into the work I am doing. Even when I am eating food I constantly scroll YouTube feed on my tablet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My review of using Windows 10 LTSC IOT for a year</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/windows10-ltsc-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/windows10-ltsc-review/</guid>
      <description>I was on Arch Linux when I decided to leave the &amp;ldquo;Linux ecosystem&amp;rdquo; and move back to Windows. I have four gigs of ram in my laptop and a SSD which is enough for my use case. I am not a super user; I use my PC to write essays, watching YouTube videos and sometimes light Photoshop work. Last year, I decided to move back to Windows because the Arch maintenance was too much for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I will not buy anything online</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/online-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/online-shopping/</guid>
      <description>This is a rant post.&#xA;I have decided to not buy or order anything from online websites like Amazon, Flipkart, Zomato, Blinkit etc. These services are not meant for convenience anymore, these websites have started charging convenience charges if you order something from them. I can let the convenience charges pass, but charging extra money for Cash On Delivery option is not good and, these charges changes according to the order&amp;rsquo;s cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am a 22-year-old guy from India who likes to read books and play football in his free time. Max used to be my Valorant username/pseudonym and now I use it everywhere on the internet. I made this website by getting inspired from several blogs on the internet, few examples are bugswriter.com, digdeeper.club, lukesmith.xyz and frugalcomputing.neocities.org. I am not a very techy guy like the people mentioned earlier but I like to learn new things.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
